<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BOOK | CRAFT</string>
    <string name="show_more">Show more</string>
    <string name="show_less">Show less</string>
    <string name="placeholder_search">Search</string>
    <dimen name="image_size">140dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="height">220dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="width">140dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="logo_size">84dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="padding_small">8dp</dimen>
    <string name="book_name_1">"To Kill a Mockingbird" by Harper Lee</string>
    <string name="book_name_2">"1984" by George Orwell</string>
    <string name="book_name_3">"The Great Gatsby" by F. Scott Fitzgerald</string>
    <string name="book_name_4">"Pride and Prejudice" by Jane Austen</string>
    <string name="book_name_5">"The Catcher in the Rye" by J.D. Salinger</string>
    <string name="book_name_6">"The Lord of the Rings" by J.R.R. Tolkien</string>
    <string name="book_name_7">"Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone" by J.K. Rowling</string>
    <string name="book_name_8">"The Hobbit" by J.R.R. Tolkien</string>
    <string name="book_name_9">"Brave New World" by Aldous Huxley</string>
    <string name="book_name_10">"Book 10</string>
    <string name="book_description_1">"To Kill a Mockingbird" is a poignant exploration of racial prejudice and moral growth in the American South during the 1930s. Through the eyes of young Scout Finch, we witness the journey of her father, Atticus Finch, as he defends an innocent Black man accused of rape. This novel is a powerful reminder of the enduring struggle for justice and the impact of compassion in a deeply divided society.</string>
    <string name="book_description_2">"1984" is a chilling dystopian masterpiece that delves into themes of totalitarianism, surveillance, and the manipulation of truth. In the oppressive society of Oceania, the protagonist Winston Smith navigates a world where Big Brother watches every move. Orwell\'s novel serves as a warning about the dangers of unchecked government power and the erosion of individual freedoms.</string>
    <string name="book_description_3">Set against the backdrop of the extravagant Jazz Age, "The Great Gatsby" is a classic tale of love, wealth, and disillusionment. Through the eyes of Nick Carraway, we enter the world of enigmatic millionaire Jay Gatsby and his unrequited love for Daisy Buchanan. Fitzgerald\'s novel explores the emptiness of materialism and the elusive American Dream.</string>
    <string name="book_description_4">"Pride and Prejudice" is a timeless romance novel that deftly satirizes societal norms and class distinctions in early 19th-century England. At its heart is the spirited Elizabeth Bennet and the brooding Mr. Darcy, whose complex courtship challenges their own prejudices and societal expectations. Austen\'s wit and insight continue to captivate readers.</string>
    <string name="book_description_5">"The Catcher in the Rye" by J.D. Salinger - Released in 1951. This book follows the journey of the disillusioned teenager Holden Caulfield as he navigates the challenges of adolescence in New York City.</string>
    <string name="book_description_6">"The Lord of the Rings" is an epic fantasy trilogy set in the richly imagined world of Middle-earth. At its core is the quest to destroy the One Ring, a symbol of ultimate power. Tolkien\'s work is a masterful blend of adventure, mythology, and themes of heroism, friendship, and the battle between good and evil.</string>
    <string name="book_description_7">The magical world of Harry Potter comes to life in this enchanting tale of a young wizard discovering his true heritage. Harry\'s journey from the cupboard under the stairs to Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry is a testament to the enduring allure of friendship, bravery, and the battle against dark forces.</string>
    <string name="book_description_8"> "The Hobbit" is a delightful adventure filled with dwarves, dragons, and one unassuming hobbit named Bilbo Baggins. As he embarks on an unexpected journey, Bilbo discovers courage and resourcefulness within himself. Tolkien\'s storytelling transports readers to a world of wonder and imagination.</string>
    <string name="book_description_9">"Brave New World" paints a chilling portrait of a highly controlled society where individuality is sacrificed for societal stability and happiness. Huxley\'s thought-provoking exploration of a future dystopia serves as a cautionary tale about the consequences of sacrificing personal freedom for societal harmony.</string>
    <string name="book_description_10">"Book 10 description</string>
    <string name="about">About:</string>
    <string name="release_date">Released in: </string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about a dog.</string>
</resources>